{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "English for Academic & Professional Purposes",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Features of Academic Text and Plagiarism",
    "LastModified": "16 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is a strategy that readers use to recall prior knowledge and set a purpose for reading?",
      "answer": "Preview",
      "choices": [
        "Review",
        "Summarize",
        "Preview",
        "Read and Understand"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Strategies for Academic Reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What means not only recognizing words, word order, and patterns, but also generating meaning through analysis and evaluation?",
      "answer": "Read and Understand",
      "choices": [
        "Preview",
        "Review",
        "Summarize",
        "Read and Understand"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Strategies for Academic Reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is used to express the most important facts or ideas about something or someone in a short and clear form?",
      "answer": "Summarize",
      "choices": [
        "Preview",
        "Review",
        "Summarize",
        "Read and Understand"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Strategies for Academic Reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is used to restate your overall opinions of the text?",
      "answer": "Review",
      "choices": [
        "Preview",
        "Review",
        "Summarize",
        "Read and Understand"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Strategies for Academic Reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the presentation of another's works or ideas as if they were your own without giving credit to the other person?",
      "answer": "Plagiarism",
      "choices": [
        "Fabrication",
        "Plagiarism",
        "Cheating",
        "Multiple Submissions"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Academic Dishonesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the word-for-word transcription of a section of someone else's work, without attribution and without quotation marks?",
      "answer": "Direct Plagiarism",
      "choices": [
        "Self Plagiarism",
        "Mosaic Plagiarism",
        "Direct Plagiarism",
        "Accidental Plagiarism"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Plagiarism"
    },
    {
      "question": "What occurs when a student submits his or her own previous work, or mixes parts of previous works, without permission from all professors involved?",
      "answer": "Self Plagiarism",
      "choices": [
        "Direct Plagiarism",
        "Self Plagiarism",
        "Mosaic Plagiarism",
        "Accidental Plagiarism"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Plagiarism"
    },
    {
      "question": "What occurs when a student borrows phrases from a source without using quotation marks, or finds synonyms for the author's language while keeping to the same general structure?",
      "answer": "Mosaic Plagiarism",
      "choices": [
        "Direct Plagiarism",
        "Self Plagiarism",
        "Mosaic Plagiarism",
        "Accidental Plagiarism"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Plagiarism"
    },
    {
      "question": "What occurs when a person neglects to cite their sources, or misquotes their sources, or unintentionally paraphrases a source by using similar words without attribution?",
      "answer": "Accidental Plagiarism",
      "choices": [
        "Direct Plagiarism",
        "Self Plagiarism",
        "Mosaic Plagiarism",
        "Accidental Plagiarism"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Types of Plagiarism"
    },
    {
      "question": "What form of academic dishonesty involves copying off of someone else's exam?",
      "answer": "Cheating",
      "choices": [
        "Fabrication",
        "Plagiarism",
        "Cheating",
        "Multiple Submissions"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Forms of Academic Dishonesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What form of academic dishonesty involves making up the results for a lab exercise?",
      "answer": "Fabrication",
      "choices": [
        "Fabrication",
        "Plagiarism",
        "Cheating",
        "Multiple Submissions"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Forms of Academic Dishonesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What form of academic dishonesty involves submitting the same paper for two classes?",
      "answer": "Multiple Submissions",
      "choices": [
        "Fabrication",
        "Plagiarism",
        "Cheating",
        "Multiple Submissions"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Forms of Academic Dishonesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "What form of academic dishonesty involves letting a roommate copy your homework?",
      "answer": "Facilitating Academic Dishonesty",
      "choices": [
        "Fabrication",
        "Facilitating Academic Dishonesty",
        "Cheating",
        "Multiple Submissions"
      ],
      "reference": "L2-ACADEMIC-TEXT.pdf",
      "term": "Forms of Academic Dishonesty"
    }
  ]
}